/*
    Identification Questions
*/

const identificationQuestions = {
    // Chapter 0: Addition and Subtraction
    0: {
        0: [
            { question: "2026 + 202 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "2228" },
            { question: "978 + 67 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "1045" },
            { question: "10459 + 45768 + 56227 = ? Type your answer:", answer: "112454" },
            
        ],
        1: [
            { question: "100 - 67 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "33" },
            { question: "98 - 231 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "-133" },
		 { question: "821 - 121 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "700" },

        ],
        2: [
            { question: "722 - 332 + 442 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "832" }
        ]
    },
    // Chapter 1: Multiplication and Division
    1: {
        0: [
            { question: "20 x 12 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "240" },
            { question: "48 × 36 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "1728" },
            { question: "150 × 84 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "12600" },
        ],
        1: [
            { question: "225 ÷ 15 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "15" },
            { question: "600 ÷ 25 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "24" },
            { question: "720 ÷ 12 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "60" },
            
            
        ],
        2: [
            { question: "320 × (-5) ÷ 40 × (-9) ÷ (-360) = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "-1" },
		 

        ]
    },
    // Chapter 2: Mixed Basic Operations
    2: {
        0: [
            { question: "8 ÷ 4 + 6 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "8" },
            { question: "36 ÷ 6 + 20 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "26" },
            { question: "12 × 5 - 18 = ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "42" },
            
        ],
        1: [
            { question: "6 × 2 - 4 + 1? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "9" },
            { question: "20 ÷ 5 + 6 × 3? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "20" },
            { question: "7 × 3 - 4 + 8? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "25" },
            
        ],
        2: [
            { question: "20 - 8 ÷ 4 + 3 × 2? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "24" },
        ]
    },
    // Chapter 3: Fundamental Notation
    3: {
        0: [
            { question: "9x - 12 = 66? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "x = 8" },
            { question: "7x + 2 = 51? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "x = 7" },        
            { question: "6x + 14 = 50? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "x = 6" },
         
            ],
        1: [
            { question: "20x + 80 = 12x + 160? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "x = 10" },
            { question: "50x - 300 = 30x + 100? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "x = 20" },
            { question: "40x - 200 = 25x + 150? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "x = 22" },
            
            
                    ],
        2: [
            { question: "x^2 - 7x + 10 = 0 ? Isulat ang iyong sagot:", answer: "x = 2 at x = 5" },
        ]
    },
    // Chapter 4: Equivalent Expressions
    4: {
        0: [
           ],
        1: [
           ],
        2: [
           ],
    }
};
